agentprovocateur.com 2017-11-10

# Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

At Agent Provocateur we are committed to maintaining your privacy. Our privacy policy statement is given below. If we make changes to this policy, we will notify you by updating this statement on our Website.

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We may ask for your name, telephone number, home address, email address age, and who you're shopping for as part of our competitions, sweepstakes, or newsletter sign ups. When a purchase is made on our site, in addition to the above, we also ask for delivery address, and payment method details. We may obtain information about your usage of our Website to help us develop and improve it further through online surveys and other requests.

### WHAT THE DATA WILL BE USED FOR?

Your data will enable us, and our processors, to fulfil your order, to notify you about important functionality changes and for statistical or survey purposes to improve this website and our services to you. We may also send you from time to time (by email or post) information about products and services and details of promotions and special offers from Agent Provocateur. If you do not wish to be contacted for these purposes, we offer a range of ways in which you can inform us about your marketing preferences:

• All email messages and email newsletters will contain information on how you can unsubscribe; or  
• Call our customer services division - [see the Contact Us section](http://www.agentprovocateur.com/gb_en/contacts/);

In assessing your request for goods or services, we may use your information for the purposes of the prevention and detection of fraud. 

### VIP DATA PROTECTION STATEMENT

We would like to use your details, plus details on how you use your VIP card and what you buy in our stores, to: Help manage the Agent Provocateur VIP card and improve the way we run it. Understand our customers’ shopping habits to improve our service. Unless you indicate otherwise, contact you with offers and information about products and services of interest to you. We will share your details among Agent Provocateur companies, and other businesses that process VIP card information on our behalf (e.g. printers who need certain details to print mailings). We may also use and share information relating to groups of customers, without identifying individuals to learn more about customer behaviour and find ways of enhancing our service. Except as required by law, or in accordance with these Terms and Conditions, your personal information will not be passed to any other persons without your permission.

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE SHARE WITH OTHERS?

We may contract with other companies to provide certain services, including credit card processing, shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, market research, marketing and advertising services (including advertising on third party websites, social media networks and profiling) and promotions management. We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Agent Provocateur. We may transfer personal data that we collect from you to third party data processors located in countries that are outside of the European Economic Area and to other companies in connection with the above purposes. Any such transfer of your personal data will be carried out in compliance with applicable laws and we will treat the information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy Statement. However, we will not pass your information on to any other company or other third parties for their own marketing purposes unless you have agreed for us to do so.

### COOKIES

This website uses Cookies. For more information please [click here to see our Cookie policy](http://www.agentprovocateur.com/gb_en/cookie-policy/).

### LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES SITES

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may from time to time include third party links on our Website. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We encourage you to review those policies when you visit those sites. This Privacy Policy Statement only covers our Website and does not cover any other website. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

### PRIVACY OF CHILDREN ON OUR WEBSITE

Our Website is intended for adult purposes and not intended for use by children under the age of 18. We will not knowingly collect any information from any person below the age of 18.

### SALE OF ASSETS

In the unlikely event that Agent Provocateur or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

### ADYEN

We work with Adyen to offer our customers more convenient methods of payment. Adyen (“Adyen”) is a provider of financial services. We need to provide Adyen with certain information about you and the order to enable Adyen to assess whether you qualify for their credit products. We need to transfer to Adyen account details such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and payment history, as well as your order details, such as payment method, shipping details, what was ordered, and similar. This will not be done if you do not select a credit or debit card as your payment method. The further use of this data will be governed by Adyen’s Privacy Policy.
